#### Contact

angie@carbergroup.com

www.linkedin.com/in/angela-carter-4450a896 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

**CSS Variables** 

Forms

CSS Flexbox

#### Certifications

Front End Development Libraries
Responsive Web Design
JavaScript Algorithms and Data
Structures

## **Angela Carter**

Manager at CARBER

Windsor, Ontario, Canada

## Summary

Over 10 years of experience as an executive coordinator, accountant, manager, data specialist, auditor, and project manager. My work specialty offers a wide variety of skill sets, normally found in large teams of people. I have used these skills to enrich and enhance small and large businesses, executives, and busy individuals alike.

I am currently seeking a better work-life - balance and to transition to a career in web development. I am interested in remote work opportunities for full or part time, short or long-term projects, and to continue to branch into new areas to keep my career interesting.

## Experience

**CARBER** 

General Manager

January 2014 - Present (9 years 7 months)

Windsor, Ontario, Canada

Manage a team of freelance individuals working together to provide a superior class of service to businesses seeking multiple skill sets across a wide spectrum. My oversight requires proficiency in project management, consulting, internal auditing, and web development. I manage the team in servicing clients in accounting, financing, tax, business management, eCommerce, web design/development, data management, and more.

**Quality Services** 

Owner

January 2015 - Present (8 years 7 months)

Windsor, Ontario

Quality Service is a property maintenance company serving residential landlords. We handle routine work like cleaning, landscaping, and seasonal repairs, along with one-off repairs like replacing doors, fixing locks, and addressing roof leaks. We are hired by Property Managers for our speed and flexibility, providing a cost-effective alternative to hiring a full-time on-

Page 1 of 3

site maintenance staff with a team that allows us to get multiple repairs and projects done in a short period of time.

Junapa Properties Incorporated
Executive Coordinator
December 2016 - January 2023 (6 years 2 months)
Windsor, Ontario, Canada

Performing tasks for senior management to support business functions and operations. Act as a liaison between tenants, team members, and the executives, sharing the employees' concerns and addressing their inquiries. Perform management duties of payroll, rent rolls, rental, tenant and vendor management. Prepare company reports, monitor business and financial transactions, and suggest project management procedures. Have excellent communication and organizational skills, especially in handling data process systems and ensuring that the information and company details on the database are accurate.

# Government of Ontario Provincial and Municipal Project Manager

April 1994 - January 2014 (19 years 10 months)

I have extensive experience in leadership roles, having managed hundreds of projects, including financial and technical initiatives that were part of the strategic goals and objectives of the Government. As an Executive Manager, I ensured compliance with regulations, identified financial risks, and improved overall efficiency by leading a team of professionals, conducting audits, analyzing data, and developing recommendations for improvement. As a Project Manager, I led projects from inception to completion, managing budgets, timelines, and team members, while communicating progress to stakeholders. As an Enterprise Risk Manager, I developed risk management strategies, conducted risk assessments, and implemented risk controls and processes to mitigate potential risks that could impact the organization's operations, reputation, or financial health. My strong analytical skills, attention to detail, and ability to communicate complex information effectively have been crucial in all of these roles.

Education

**ABM College** 

Web Design and Development / Full Stack Developer, Web Page, Digital/ Multimedia and Information Resources Design · (September 2022 - August 2023)

University of Windsor

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Accounting and
Finance · (1981 - 1983)

### St. Clair College

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Accounting and Business/ Management · (September 1978 - 1981)